Guide to the Time Inc. Reference Files 1907-2015 (bulk 1933-2003) MS 3009-RG 3
New-York Historical Society
- Time Warner Inc.: Subsidaries List: 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 577, Folder 1-2)
- Time Warner Inc.: Subsidaries List: 1991- (Offsite-box 576, Folder 17-19)
- Time Warner Inc.: Subsidaries List: 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 577, Folder 3-5)
- Time Warner Inc.: Subsidaries List: 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 577, Folder 6)
- Time Warner Inc.: Misc. (Offsite-box 577, Folder 7)
- Time Warner: Keywords: Employee Newsletter: 2005 (Offsite-box 577, Folder 8)
- Time Warner: Trade Publishing (Offsite-box 577, Folder 9)
- Time Warner: Week in Review: June 19, 2000-December 29, 2000 (Offsite-box 577, Folder 10)
- AOL Time Warner: In the News: January 2001- (Offsite-box 577, Folder 11)
- AOL Time Warner: Week in Review: 2002 (Offsite-box 577, Folder 12)
- AOL Time Warner: New this week on Info Center (Offsite-box 577, Folder 13)
- AOL Time Warner: Week In Review: 2003 (Offsite-box 577, Folder 14)
- Time Warner Corporate Communications: Time Warner Week in Review: 2004 (Offsite-box 577, Folder 15)
- Time Warner Corporate Communications: Time Warner Week in Review: 2005 (Offsite-box 577, Folder 16)
- Time Warner Corporate Communications: Time Warner Week in Review: 2006 (Offsite-box 577, Folder 17)
- Time Warner Corporate Communications: Time Warner Week in Review: 2007 (Offsite-box 578, Folder 1)
- Time Warner Corporate Communications: Time Warner Week in Review: 2008 (Offsite-box 578, Folder 2-3)
- Time Warner Corporate Communications: Time Warner Week in Review: 2009 (Offsite-box 578, Folder 4)
- Time Warner Corporate Communications: Time Warner Week in Review: 2010 (Offsite-box 578, Folder 5)
- Time Warner Corporate Communications: Time Warner Week in Review: 2011 (Offsite-box 578, Folder 6)
- Travel and Leisure: Misc. (Offsite-box 578, Folder 7)
- Treasurer's Office (Offsite-box 578, Folder 8)
- Turner Broadcasting System Inc. (Offsite-box 578, Folder 9-10)
- TV-Cable Week: Advertising Rate Cards (Offsite-box 578, Folder 11)
- TV-Cable Week: Misc. (Offsite-box 578, Folder 12)
- TWX: Misc.: January 1998-September/October 2000 (Offsite-box 578, Folder 13)
- Vibe: Misc. (Offsite-box 578, Folder 14)
- Video Group (Offsite-box 578, Folder 15)
- Wallpaper and Wallpaper Group: Misc.: 1997 (Offsite-box 578, Folder 16)
- Wardell Reports: Misc. (Offsite-box 578, Folder 17)
- Warner Brothers: Hollywood Reporter 75th Anniversary Issue photocopy: September 1998 (Offsite-box 578, Folder 18)
- Warner Books: Misc. (Offsite-box 578, Folder 19)
- Warner Communications: Warner Brothers: Animation (Offsite-box 578, Folder 20)
- Warner Communications: Warner Brothers: Misc. (Offsite-box 578, Folder 21)
- Warner Communications: Warner Brothers: History (Offsite-box 578, Folder 22-23)
- Warner Communications: Warner Brothers: Television: Production and Distribution (Offsite-box 578, Folder 24)
- Warner Communications: Warner Brothers: Television: The WB Network (Offsite-box 578, Folder 25)
- Warner Communications: Misc. (Offsite-box 578, Folder 26)
- Warner Home Video (Offsite-box 579, Folder 1)
- Warner Music Group (Offsite-box 579, Folder 2-3)
- Washington Star (Offsite-box 579, Folder 4-5)
- Weight Watchers (Southern Progress title) (Offsite-box 579, Folder 6)
- Whittle Communications: Misc. (Offsite-box 579, Folder 7)
- Whittle Communications: Channel 1 (Offsite-box 579, Folder 8)
- Yazhou Zhoukan: Misc. (Offsite-box 579, Folder 9)